<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Misc -->

  <Concrete.label>Τσιμέντο concrete</Concrete.label>
  <Concrete.description>Κακοστρωμένο τσιμέντο. Περπατάς γρήγορα πάνω του όμως είναι άσχημο. Πρέπει πρώτα να σκάψεις το έδαφος για να το στρώσεις Quick-poured concrete. Fast to walk on, cheap, and very quick to pour, but quite ugly.</Concrete.description>

  <PavedTile.label>Πλακόστρωμα paved tile</PavedTile.label>
  <PavedTile.description>Επίστρωση από τσιμέντο. Γρήγορη μετακίνηση πάνο του αλλά φαίνεται άσχημο Utilitarian concrete tiles. Cheap and quick to move around on, but neutral in terms of looks and slow to build.</PavedTile.description>

  <WoodPlankFloor.label>Ξύλινο πάτωμα wood floor</WoodPlankFloor.label>
  <WoodPlankFloor.description>Ξύλινη επίστρωση. Γι'αυτήν τηνο θερμή, σπιτική αίσθηση. Wood plank flooring. For that warm, homey feeling. While it is easy to lay, it is also flammable.</WoodPlankFloor.description>

  <MetalTile.label>Μεταλικά Πλακάκια metal tile</MetalTile.label>
  <MetalTile.description>Μεταλικά πλακάκια, για διακόσμιση παρόμοια με διαστιμοπλοίου! Metal tiles, for that spaceship look. Pretty, but labor and material-intensive.</MetalTile.description>

  <SilverTile.label>silver tile</SilverTile.label>
  <SilverTile.description>Expensive and slow to build, but very pretty. Fits perfectly into luxurious rooms.</SilverTile.description>

  <GoldTile.label>gold tile</GoldTile.label>
  <GoldTile.description>The most beautiful and impressive kind of floor. Very expensive and requires a lot of work to build.</GoldTile.description>

  <SterileTile.label>sterile tile</SterileTile.label>
  <SterileTile.description>Sterile tiles help keep the room clean. Very useful in hospitals to prevent patients from getting various infections. Neutral in terms of looks and very slow to build.</SterileTile.description>


  <!-- Carpets -->

  <CarpetRed.label>Κόκκινο Χαλί red carpet</CarpetRed.label>
  <CarpetRed.description>Βελούδινο χαλί σε πανέμορφη κόκκινη απόχρωση Plush carpet in a lovely rose hue.</CarpetRed.description>

  <CarpetGreen.label>Πράσινο Χαλί green carpet</CarpetGreen.label>
  <CarpetGreen.description>Πράσινο χαλί στο χρώμα της φύσης Naturalistic-feeling green carpet.</CarpetGreen.description>

  <CarpetBlue.label>Μπλέ Χαλί blue carpet</CarpetBlue.label>
  <CarpetBlue.description>Το βελούδινο χαλί που αγκαλιάζει τα δάχτυλα των ποδιών σε ένα σαγηνευτικό μπλέ χρώμαToe-hugging plush carpet in a cool blue color.</CarpetBlue.description>

  <CarpetCream.label>cream carpet</CarpetCream.label>
  <CarpetCream.description>Inviting cream-colored carpet.</CarpetCream.description>

  <CarpetDark.label>dark carpet</CarpetDark.label>
  <CarpetDark.description>Professional-looking dark gray carpet.</CarpetDark.description>


</LanguageData>